{"id": "3Q9SPIIRWJKVQ8244310E8TUS6YWAC##34V1S5K3GTZMDUBNBIGY93FLDOB690##A1S1K7134S2VUC##Blog_1044056##q1_a1##3XU9MCX6VQQG7YPLCSAFDPQNH4GR20", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Good Old War and person L : I saw both of these bands Wednesday night , and they both blew me away . seriously . Good Old War is acoustic and makes me smile . I really can not help but be happy when I listen to them ; I think it 's the fact that they seemed so happy themselves when they played .\n\nQuestion: In the future , will this person go to see other bands play ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "This person likes music and likes to see the show , they will see other bands play .", "C": "This person only likes Good Old War and Person L , no other bands .", "D": "Other Bands is not on tour and this person can not see them ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 0, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3E24UO25QZOMYXHZN4TEH9EMT9GO6L##3UN61F00HXNWYQ7V0G6F8I1FMXXR5I##AO33H4GL9KZX9##Blog_292639##q1_a1##375VMB7D4LXQH9KIJU0NVGG0RV5ID7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I mean it : not one person said ANYTHING to me . They would have if I did something wrong , right ? But , this morning , I got a call from my guy at the temp agency and he said that I was no longer needed in that position , that I did n't need to go out there .\n\nQuestion: Why might have the temp agency tell me I am not needed at that position ?", "options": {"A": "The company hiring the temp workers might have had a change of mind .", "B": "The temp agency hiring the temp workers might have had a change of mind .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "I might have had a change of mind working for the company ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 1, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3M4KL7H8KVL125AYH2V35D1E0A016T##3SB5N7Y3O426ETCGNZ6RSJRH4ZY0G0##AJ7NSZOAFP05U##Blog_254278##q1_a1##3IH9TRB0FDDWPE4631GSUEFR22K1IQ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Leaving my shift Thursday day shift I arrived the same time as my partner just after six that evening and before long the radio erupted in dispatch tones . A car fleeing the police has crashed and landed on its roof with four separate people entrapped inside . Our medic unit is dispatched along with multiple other ambulances and Rescue Companies .\n\nQuestion: What may have caused the radio to erupt with dispatch tones ?", "options": {"A": "My partner needed a medic unit .", "B": "Someone was running from the ambulances after they got into a wreck .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "Someone was running from the cops and got into a wreck ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 2, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3D5G8J4N5CI2K40F4RZLF9OG2L4VTJ##34MAJL3QP721EUH0VIY9DQGUNNO34F##A2KYOM2ZGYDJGT##Blog_536416##q1_a1##3LAZVA75NK5DALX5K0TBJULI6KY2OA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So , last day in Seattle , and my flight was at 1:30 . I got to chit chat with my old manager ( more like a mentor ) , and left Seattle feeling really good and inspired . .\n\nQuestion: Why did I chit chat with my old manager ?", "options": {"A": "Because my flight was at 1:30 .", "B": "Because I left Seattle feeling really good and inspired .", "C": "Because it 's my last day in Seattle .", "D": "Because I enjoy talking to him ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3MQKOF1EE428I44N8B42W7P86DKDW4##3NJM2BJS4ZLBGNZ2MV1Y9RVJLN5PCH##A2KYOM2ZGYDJGT##Blog_778772##q1_a1##3PCPFX4U4240WRMXN80MSIA8V4WFQN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Ms. Mumma informed Mr. Dail that evidence had been found in his case . \" I fell out of my chair and burst into tears . Evidence meant I was going home , and I knew that , \" said Mr. Dail . He immediately told Ms. Mumma , \" Test anything and everything you can find .\n\nQuestion: Why did I burst into tears ?", "options": {"A": "Because Ms. Mumma was informative .", "B": "Because I had an intense emotional response to the new development .", "C": "Because Mr. Dail was informed .", "D": "Because I fell out of my chair ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 4, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "341H3G5YF0C3JQ9RNOOEO6BZ01T0ZC##3TU5ZICBREZF97BXLZOIFC11QLW8Q2##A2KYOM2ZGYDJGT##Blog_362252##q1_a1##3N3WJQXELU4540U878DJRDHOB2D2LN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "A while later I tried the car again and lo and behold it does n't start at all , so a tow truck was called , and I chatted with Ellen ( who was n't in class after all ) while I waited . My dad came and got me from the body shop . The End . ( Where the hell did my freaking cow go ?\n\nQuestion: What is n't working properly ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "The cow", "C": "The tow truck", "D": "The body shop"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 5, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3CMIQF80GNOPJ9UF2HLI6E9M8FM6Q9##3RKNTXVS3NWM3QHEK01J806RNPS4AH##A2KYOM2ZGYDJGT##Blog_247332##q1_a1##3BDORL6HKMRT5GHN9LZLP2Z9TTYCRV", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Until we went to a playdate two weeks ago . Thea 's mom is Serbian and crepes are apparently as common in Serbia as they are in France . We discussed the batter , the texture , the cooking process , the topping options and Dee generally brought me up to speed . Being not brave enough to just start throwing ingredients in a bowl as she did , I got a recipe of the internet for general proportions , ended up not using nearly as much water as was called for and successfully made crepes .\n\nQuestion: Why did they discuss crepes ?", "options": {"A": "Because Thea 's mom is Serbian .", "B": "Because the writer got a recipe from the internet .", "C": "Because the writer is interested in learning how to cook crepes .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 6, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3G9UA71JVVSR1M47Q161FRXWPX17J9##3O6CYIULEEZIR1EW0BOT3T1CERNUWL##A1OPGPTQJ48XOY##Blog_334171##q1_a1##3NFWQRSHVGS9J2SJKCVAY465OXJGFI", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Let me be clear , everything is good . Having said that , I ' ve been a little preoccupied lately , as Leslie threw out her back on Sunday . It 's been an interesting , and marriage - solidifying 36 hours . Sunday afternoon , around 2 pm , Leslie and I were hanging in the library , sans kids ( they were with their father ) , listening to music and talking .\n\nQuestion: How did Leslie 's throwing out of her back help to solidify your marriage ?", "options": {"A": "Leslie realized that I am really good at taking care of people and wants to keep me around for that reason", "B": "Leslie saw that if she ever hurt herself she would need my help to heal and realized that she needs me", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "We were able to spend time together just talking and that helped us to connect better"}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3OLZC0DJ8JDXH1LXQHOH94YZY2IVIG##36H9ULYP63S72ZH7YNAFS3612HNFJI##A1S1K7134S2VUC##Blog_113481##q1_a1##3KLL7H3EGFFCFV9K4XIW1QLSRTOVHS", "type": "mcq", "stem": "WHAT could be in the package ? Something PORNOGRAPHIC , that 's for sure ! I rushed into the house and went to the laundry room , closed the door and pulled the package out of the magazine . I flipped it over , and reread the words on the side . Contains PHOTOGRAPHIC material . Damn .\n\nQuestion: Why is this person disappointed that they misread the label on the package ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "Pornographic implies something forbidden , this person was exited by the thought .", "C": "The person ordered a package of pornographic material and anticipated its arrival .", "D": "The material inside the package contains ordinary pornography , not a magazine ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 8, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3OLZC0DJ8JDXH1LXQHOH94YZY2IVIG##36H9ULYP63S72ZH7YNAFS3612HNFJI##A1S1K7134S2VUC##Blog_113481##q1_a2##3R5OYNIC2ENPFK3JIFQM9HZYGZITPF", "type": "mcq", "stem": "WHAT could be in the package ? Something PORNOGRAPHIC , that 's for sure ! I rushed into the house and went to the laundry room , closed the door and pulled the package out of the magazine . I flipped it over , and reread the words on the side . Contains PHOTOGRAPHIC material . Damn .\n\nQuestion: Why is this person disappointed that they misread the label on the package ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "The material inside the package contains ordinary pornography , not a magazine .", "C": "The person ordered a package of pornographic material and anticipated its arrival .", "D": "The misread label made the person think the package contains something forbidden , the truth was dull ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3MQY1YVHS3IEX29PWXCPLCXB637B2V##386PBUZZXGVT2RR3KYDDNGBLYZNLJE##AJ7NSZOAFP05U##Blog_627768##q1_a1##3ZC62PVYDJO15AEU9G10SX67VPAXXB", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Last night , the roomie and I were both feeling pretty mellow . My week has been over scheduled , and it wore me out and prevented me from working one day . So I did n't make plans for Friday night , much as I wanted to . Instead , we went with our moods . And our moods said , \" hey , why do n't we go out for ice cream , walk to the video store , rent a movie , walk to the firehouse , chat up Fireman Dave and then walk home to watch the movie ? \"\n\nQuestion: What may have been the reason for you and your roommate wanting a mellow night ?", "options": {"A": "I was n't doing too much work that week .", "B": "I was burnt out from too much work .", "C": "My roommate was burnt out from too much work .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 10, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3LOJFQ4BOZTHN4A6JXLZ8WVDJZWDKF##3SITXWYCNYOXFR9NUMFKSKB441UXBL##A2KYOM2ZGYDJGT##Blog_302465##q1_a1##35ZRNT9RUKC2V3TOO07G24QACYBO3K", "type": "mcq", "stem": "It has been roughly a month since my last post and so understandably a lot has taken place . I finished my time in France with a tough week that left me fatigued and I was more than glad to be returning home . August 12th was when I made my trip from Lyon to Frankfurt to Calgary and finally Edmonton .\n\nQuestion: Why has it been roughly a month since my last post ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "Because a tough week left me fatigued .", "C": "Because I finished my time in France .", "D": "Because I 've been busy with other things ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3RQVKZ7ZRMX6PF563EC988ZNFSP72J##3DIP6YHAPF757TKZW55IDT0WD7ME8F##AJ7NSZOAFP05U##Blog_1096124##q1_a1##34KYK9TV2TMMWQPUAA3V4SYNXA8BS2", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Hi there , Friday 22nd August - I went to the Panic At The Disco concert at Acer Arena . It was really good . I was n't too sure on Panic because I do n't know a lot of songs off their new album , but they played the ones that I knew , and quite a few old ones which I also knew . Apart from the crappy first band , Cobra Starship played first and they were really good .\n\nQuestion: What may happen if you go the Panic At The Disco concert ?", "options": {"A": "I would think that it 's pleasant .", "B": "I 'd want the first band to play more .", "C": "I would think that it is n't pleasant .", "D": "I would wish that I saw Cobra Starship instead of Panic At The Disco ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 12, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "32204AGAADQTXYJPF2JA1PII4EKGH8##31UV0MXWNTRY0G3JUQO6MOOX6G55I5##A33PQXKQHFVF3V##Blog_90103##q1_a1##3W31J70BAUA7IC4SJ1QOOQDVY7KKC2", "type": "mcq", "stem": "But the thing is , I forgave and forgot a while ago . I ' m not bitter anymore . I just genuinely do n't want to go back to that church . I could n't get the balls to tell her that ...\n\nQuestion: Why would n't I have the balls to tell her that ?", "options": {"A": "I am not a man and I ca n't tell her those things to her face .", "B": "I am afraid of that church and I would feel less manly if I told her .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "It is her favorite church and I do n't want to hurt her feelings ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 13, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3OJX0UFJ0Z54TL3UHX8Z0PXD1WD9UV##32SCWG5HII275HRUS7CVVTF0HAH6PI##A2CMYWI1J292YJ##Blog_1257072##q1_a1##39I4RL8QGLVDLIQ5K1H9S0LFE5XH40", "type": "mcq", "stem": "This July , a New York City police officer and a cyclist had an altercation of some sort . The cop claimed the man had been weaving in and out of traffic and tried to hit him with his bike , and arrested him for assault , resisting arrest , and disorderly conduct . The man said the cop had shoved him off his bike for no reason .\n\nQuestion: What kind of person is this New York City police officer ?", "options": {"A": "even tempered", "B": "polite and decent", "C": "aggressive and menacing", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 14, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3OJX0UFJ0Z54TL3UHX8Z0PXD1WD9UV##32SCWG5HII275HRUS7CVVTF0HAH6PI##A2CMYWI1J292YJ##Blog_1257072##q2_a1##3KG2UQJ0ML2CKJZELWJZ0NJGW9OQN0", "type": "mcq", "stem": "This July , a New York City police officer and a cyclist had an altercation of some sort . The cop claimed the man had been weaving in and out of traffic and tried to hit him with his bike , and arrested him for assault , resisting arrest , and disorderly conduct . The man said the cop had shoved him off his bike for no reason .\n\nQuestion: What was this New York City police officer doing before the incident ?", "options": {"A": "He was walking or standing on street .", "B": "He was on a bicycle .", "C": "He was driving a car .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 15, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3OJX0UFJ0Z54TL3UHX8Z0PXD1WD9UV##32SCWG5HII275HRUS7CVVTF0HAH6PI##A2CMYWI1J292YJ##Blog_1257072##q2_a1##3P888QFVX58U24ZQMBJCFCJLMJTQOF", "type": "mcq", "stem": "This July , a New York City police officer and a cyclist had an altercation of some sort . The cop claimed the man had been weaving in and out of traffic and tried to hit him with his bike , and arrested him for assault , resisting arrest , and disorderly conduct . The man said the cop had shoved him off his bike for no reason .\n\nQuestion: What was this New York City police officer doing before the incident ?", "options": {"A": "He was on a bicycle .", "B": "He was driving a car .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "He was on foot ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 16, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3OID399FXG5RDTJLYOI20LF0IZZDFD##3WQQ9FUS6BSS51982HRSKN627WKB87##AJ7NSZOAFP05U##Blog_455607##q1_a1##3P4ZBJFX2XH5GOIJZHZSK7STIL5FWC", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Sadly he is no where the DJ he is producer and his set was full of mediocre mixes and rather poorly programmed electro and tech house . That said , I danced to most of his set and enjoyed it , but compared to JDS and Rennie , mang it d be hard for anyone to step up . Was cool to see him though .\n\nQuestion: What may be true about him as a DJ ?", "options": {"A": "His music is average .", "B": "His music was better than JDS 's set .", "C": "He stopped making mixes .", "D": "His music is n't even average ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 17, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3HO4MYYR12MHB21WJQ5NGF6BBV4U64##3QFUFYSY9ZDHZHYMVGNBM1HIJA6F4F##AO33H4GL9KZX9##Blog_124012##q1_a1##3XH7ZM9YX48R7IAKX1PUNCY1N699RL", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I ask tough questions during my critique . It is easy to fall in love with your ideas , which is why it is imperative that you have an outsider review and critique your plan . This process will help you uncover weaknesses that you may not perceive in your business plan .\n\nQuestion: What might I continue to do after this ?", "options": {"A": "I might continue to critique the business idea to discover the weaknesses .", "B": "I might stop to critique the business idea to discover the weaknesses .", "C": "I might continue to critique the business idea to discover the strengths .", "D": "I might ease up on critiques on the business idea to discover the weaknesses ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 18, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "33TGB4G0LPFFU463K8O3BWXTPLWXTA##3HPZF4IVNNRQUCSWTLLHUK0MH1QCY5##A1I72NHC21347A##Blog_114581##q1_a1##3TL87MO8CO3P5U6KV3SQBWBDKCFLFZ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Sensible people would have checked the weather or preemptively backed the truck into the carport . But that 's not the kind of people we are , so I pulled on a sweatshirt , backed the other two cars out of the driveway , and had Mike back the truck in safely . I hope our neighbors were entertained . My pajamas legs were soaked .\n\nQuestion: what may have happened before this event ?", "options": {"A": "The pickup fit around the cars and into carport", "B": "We left the truck and its load just get rained on", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "The cars were in the drive so we left the pickup truck , with its load , at end of drive"}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19, "label_index": 3}}
